Ross, she wants you.
저 여자 분명히
너한테 관심 있어
We just live in the same building.
같은 아파트에 살면서
그저 안면만 있어
-Any contact?
-She lent me an egg.
- 그것 뿐이야?
- 계란을 꾼 적은 있지
-You're in!
-Right.
다 됐네!
무슨... 맞아!
Hey, Ross.
안녕, 로스!
안녕!
Come on. Get back in the game.
너도 연애는 하고 살아야지
레이첼도 물 건너갔고
전처는 레즈비언이고...
The Rachel thing isn't happening,
your ex-wife's a lesbian....
I don't think we need a third.
세 번째는 뭐가 올까?
계란 좀 부탁할게요
후라이 말구요, 고마워요
Could we get an egg,
still in the shell?
An egg?
계란?
저 여자한테 가서...
Go up to her and say,
"I'm returning your egg."
"여기 계란 있어요
빌린 걸 갚습니다"
I think it's winning.
틀림없이 된다!
- 그건 말이 안돼
- 좋아할 거야
-It's insane.
-She'll love it.
-Thank you.
-Thank you. Here.
- 고마워요
- 고마워, 받아
Go with the egg, my friend.
계란 받게, 친구!
Go, go, go!
어서 가, 가, 가!
효과가 있을까?
-Think it'll work?
-No way. It's suicide.
없지! 자살행위야
계란으로 꼬셔?
The One With The Candy Hearts
- 절대 안돼!
- 뭔데 그래?
-You can't do this.
-Do what?
내일 밤에 로저를 만난대
-Roger wants to take her out.
-No! Remember why you dumped him?
안돼, 피비
로저랑 헤어진 이유를 잊었니?
Because he was creepy.
괴상하지
심술 맞고
좀 두렵기도 해
And mean. And frightening.
그래도 발렌타인 데이에
혼자 있긴 싫어
Still, it's nice to have
a date on Valentine's Day!
- 안녕
- 왔니?
You can go out with a creep any night.
그런 괴팍한 남자는
아무 때나 만나면 돼
해봐서 알지
I know I do.
- 안녕
-What are you doing tomorrow night?
-That depends on how tonight goes.
너희들 내일 뭐하니?
오늘을 어떻게
보내느냐에 달렸지
잠깐, 그거 말이야...
-About tonight
-Don't you bail on me!
안돼! 배신 때리지 마
I said I'd bring a friend
for her friend.
내가 데이트할 여자는
자기 친구 짝이 있어야 된댔어
- 근데 그 여자의 친구가 좀...
- 좀 이상하대
-But her friend sounds like a
-Pathetic mess. I know, but....
그래도 착해서 상처를
잘 받는대
Come on. She's needy, vulnerable.
I'm thinking....
Thanks.
고마워
제니스 이후에 데이트한 적
없으니까 이번엔 꼭 해야돼
You haven't been out with a woman
since Janice. You're doing this.
- 왔니?
- 안녕
- 좋다더라
- 잘 됐어
-She said yes.
-Way to go, man!
해냈구나!
- 계란은 안 줬니?
- 응
Still got the egg, huh?
How do I look?
나 어때?
I don't care.
신경 안 써
There's Lorraine.
로레인이다
짝은 안 바꾼댔지?
넌 이쁜 짝, 난 폭탄 짝
No trading. You get the pretty one,
I get the mess.
- 안녕, 조이
- 안녕
Hi, Joey.
Well, well!
Look what you brought!
어머...
짝꿍 한번 근사하네!
멋져요!
Very nice.
And what did you bring?
그 쪽 짝꿍은요?
She's checking her coat.
코트 맡기고 올 거예요
I'm gonna wash the cab smell
off of my hands.
손 좀 씻고 올게
고양이 냄새 때문에
Get me a white zinfandel,
and a glass of red for Janice.
주문 좀 해줘, 난 백포도주
제니스는 적포도주로!
Janice?
제니스?
Janice!?
맙, 소, 사!
Oh...
... my...
...God!
Hey, it's Janice!
안녕, 제니스!
도망가고 싶어
창문에서 뛰어내릴까?
Okay, I'm making a break for it!
I've been waiting for, like, forever
to go out with Lorraine.
안돼, 제발 좀...
로레인과 만날 오늘을
얼마나 기다렸는지 알아?
- 진정해!
- 진정하라구?
-Just calm down.
-Calm down?
5개월간 두 번이나 차버린
여자를 만나게 해놓고?
You set me up with a woman I've
dumped twice in the last five months!
소리 좀 그만 질러
자꾸 긴장되잖아
Can you stop yelling?
You're making me nervous and....
I can't go when I'm nervous.
긴장하면 못 싼다구
I'm sorry, you're right.
미안해, 알았어
야! 빨리 싸!
빨리!
Come on! Do it, do it!
Roger was creepy, but he was nothing
compared to Pete.
로저가 괴상하긴 해도
피트보단 훨씬 나아
피트가 누구야?
-Who?
-Pete the Weeper.
울보 피트!
The guy that used to cry
every time we had sex?
같이 잘 때마다
늘 울던 남자 있잖아
"Was it good for you?"
이번엔 좋았지?
I'd take crying any day
over Howard, the "I win" guy!
난 '승리의 사나이'만
생각하면 울고싶어져
"I win! I win!"
승리다! 이겼어!
그 남자를 만나는 동안
난 승리의 기쁨을 못 느꼈어
We went out for two months.
I didn't win once.
그런 괴짜들하고 어떻게 끝냈지?
친구들이 도와서 그래
How do we end up with these jerks?
We're some kind of magnets.
우리는 서로를 당겨주는
자석 같은 친구야
I know I am. That's why I can't
wear a digital watch.
자석 맞아
그래서 내가 시계를 안 차잖아
There's more beer, right?
내 맥주는 남아있어?
You know my friend who shaves her head?
내 친구 애비 알지?
삭발한 애
아니
No.
그래, 애비가 머리를 삭발한 애야
I have this friend
who shaves her head.
She says to break the
bad boyfriend cycle...
이상한 남자가 자꾸 꼬이면
정화의식 같은 게 필요하대
...you can do a cleansing ritual.
그 친구는 자발적으로
삭발한 거잖아
Pheebs, this woman
is voluntarily bald.
맞아!
Yeah.
We can do it tomorrow night.
내일 밤에 우리도 하자
발렌타인 데이면 딱이야
It's Valentine's Day.
It's perfect.
Okay, what kind of ritual?
좋아, 어떤 의식?
남자들에게 받은
물건을 모두 태우자
We can burn the stuff they gave us.
Or...?
또는?
Or we can chant and dance
around naked with sticks.
또는... 노래하고 춤추자
발가벗고, 막대도 들고
Burning's good.
- 태우기로 하자
- 그게 좋겠어
You know...
난... 어릴 적부터 발가락으로
동전을 집어 올렸어
... I can pick up quarters with my toes.
Yeah?
Good for you.
그래?
좋겠다
Quarters or rolls of quarters?
살살 굴리기도 했어?
있잖아, 챈들러
By the way, I cut you out of
all of my pictures.
사진 속의 네 얼굴을
죄다 오려냈어
So if you want, I have a bag
with just your heads.
얼굴만 모아놓은 거
원하면 가져가!
That's okay.
됐어
그래? 정말?
인형에 그 얼굴들을 붙여서...
You could make little puppets
out of them.
And you could use them in your
Theater of Cruelty!
'잔인한 얼굴'이라는
인형극이나 만드시지!
그건 안 되지!
-We can't do that!
-What? What can't you do?
뭐가 안 되는데?
잠깐 얘기 좀 하자
저기서
Can I talk to you for a second?
Over there?
We might be leaving now.
우리 지금 가야겠어
Tell me it's you and me "we."
제발 나도 끌고 가
로레인이 내 몸에 뭔가를
듬뿍 바르고 핥아준대
She wants to slather my body
with stuff and lick it off.
뭘 바를지 너무 궁금해!
I'm not even sure what slathering is!
빨랑 알고 싶어 환장하겠다
But I definitely want
to be a part of it!
Okay, you cannot do this to me.
나한테 그럴 순 없지!
- 알았어, 미안해
- 그래...
You're right. I'm sorry.
Can we have three
chocolate mousses to go?
초콜릿 크림 좀
싸주시겠어요?
지금 갈게
I'm out of here.
카드 줄 테니까
저녁 값 내, 미안해
Here's my credit card.
Dinner's on me.
초콜릿 먹고
이빨이나 썩어라!
I hope she throws up on you.
Thanks.
고마워
그럼...
-So....
-Just us.
우리 뿐이야
죽이는 밤이군!
What a crappy night!
난 정말 즐거웠는데
I have enjoyed the fact...
아까 화장실 다녀온 뒤
계속 지퍼가 열려있었거든
...that your shirt's been
sticking out of your zipper.
실례
Excuse me.
How you doing?
안녕하세요?
So do we have the best friends,
or what?
친구 한번 잘 뒀지?
조이는 친구도 아냐
녀석이...
Joey's not a friend.
He's...
멍청하게 카드를 주고 갔어!
...a stupid man who left us
his credit card.
Another drink? Dessert?
A big-screen TV?
술 더 마실까?
안주도?
-I'll have a drink.
-Got it. Good woman!
- 술 한 잔 더하지
- 좋아, 똑똑한 여자야!
세금 왕창 붙은
최고급 샴페인 주세요
-A bottle of overpriced champagne.
-Each.
- 두 병이요
- 네, 두 병이요
That's right, each.
And a rob roy.
로브로이 칵테일도요
마셔보고 싶었어
I've always wanted to know.
Happy Valentine's Day!
발렌타인 데이 아침이야!
자기, 벌써 그리워
Oh, I miss you already.
어제 일이 믿겨져?
-Can you believe this happened?
-No, no!
아니, 안돼!
And yet it did.
믿을 수가 없어!
-Goodbye, Janice.
-kiss me!
- 잘 자, 제니스
- 키스해야지
Oh, Chandler. Sorry.
챈들러, 미안해
챈들러... 미안혀!
Oh, Chandler. Sorry!
-Hey, Janice.
-Hi, Monica.
- 안녕, 제니스
- 안녕, 모니카
Well, this was very special.
아주 특별한 경우다
레이첼, 나와 봐!
Rach, come see who's out here!
왜 그래?
세상에!
What's going on? Oh, my God!
- 제니스, 안녕!
- 안녕
Janice! Hi!
Janice is gonna go away now!
막 가려던 참이야
I'll be right back.
금방 올게
조이! 누군지 봐!
Joey! Look who it is!
드디어 조이가 왔구나
Good. Joey's home.
너무 즐겁다!
복도에서의 재회라니!
This is so much fun!
This is like a reunion in the hall!
Ross, there's someone
I want you to say hi to.
안녕, 오빠
여기 친구랑 인사 좀 해
He happened to call.
갑자기 전화가 왔어
안녕, 로스! 맞아, 나야!
어떻게 알았어?
Hi, Ross. That's right, it's me!
How did you know?
개가 시차로 인한 피로를
느낀다고 칩시다
So, if dogs experience jet lag...
인간의 1년은 개에게
7년이거든요
... because of the seven dog years
to one human year thing...
그럼, 뉴욕에서 LA로 갈 때
3시간 시차가 아니라
...when a dog flies
from New York to Los Angeles...
... he doesn't just lose three hours,
he loses a week and a half.
개는 일주일 정도의 시차죠
- 재밌네요
- 네
That's funny!
- 이따가 여기서 요리를 보여줘요
- 네, 좋아요
They should be cooking the food soon.
Oh, good.
왜 그래요?
Who are they?
누군데요?
금발은 이혼한 전처고...
The blond is my ex-wife.
The woman touching her is her...
전처를 만지고 있는 여자는
사적으로 친한 사이죠
...close, personal friend.
연인 사이란 거죠?
-They're lovers?
-lf you want to put a label on it.
그런 단어도 있군요
- 더할 말씀 없어요?
- 없어요, 그게 전부죠
-Anything else I should know?
-Nope. That's it.
내 아기를 임신하고 있죠
Oh, and she's pregnant with my baby.
늘 잊어먹고 산다니까요
I always forget that part.
Hello!
안녕!
Now we need sage branches
and the sacramental wine.
이제, 샐비어 잎과
새크라멘토 포도주가 필요해
All I had is oregano and a Fresca.
오레가노 잎과
프레스카 포도주 뿐이야
That's okay!
- 그것도 괜찮아
- 그래
Now we need the semen
of a righteous man.
이제, 좋은 남자의
정액이 필요해
그런 남자를 만났으면
이런 의식을 왜 하겠니?
If we had that, we wouldn't be doing
the ritual in the first place.
-Can we start throwing things in?
-Yeah, okay!
그냥 태우면 안돼?
그래, 좋아
됐어!
이건, 베리의 편지
Okay.
Barry's letters.
아담 리터의 팬티
Adam Ritter's boxer shorts.
And I have the receipt
from my dinner with....
내가 가진 건
저녁 영수증이야
이름은 콜룰루아카
-A picture of Scotty Jared naked!
-Let me see!
스카티의 벗은 사진이야
어디 봐!
스웨터는 입었네
-He's wearing a sweater.
-No.
잘 봐
- 잠깐만, 여기 무슨 카드가 있어
- 내 거야
-Whose MCl card is that?
-Mine. Shoot!
번호만 알면 돼
974-3...
Remember this number:
Nine, seven, four....
다 탔네
마지막으로 파올로의 술병!
Okay, and here we have
the last of Paolo's grappa.
잠깐!
그거 알콜 도수가...
Wait, isn't it almost pure
How can I dump this woman
on Valentine's Day?
어떻게 발렌타인 데이에
여자를 차냐?
글쎄, 1월 1일에도 찼었잖아
I don't know.
You dumped her on New Year's.
In my next life,
I'm coming back as a toilet brush.
내세가 있다면
변기통으로 태어날 거야
안녕, 나의 발렌타인!
Hello, funny valentine!
안녕, 그냥 제니스!
Hi, just Janice.
안녕, 조이
우리를 이어준 중매쟁이!
Hello, Joey, our little matchmaker.
너무 이뻐서
뽀뽀해주고 싶어 죽겠어
I could just kiss you all over,
and I'm gonna.
됐어
If you don't do it, I will.
네가 안 하면
내가 차겠어
근데... 정말 뉴욕 출신이세요?
-So are you actually from New York?
-Not originally. I'm from
아니에요, 원래는...
이런, 맙소사
안돼, 네가 없어도 된다고 했잖아
-You said they'd shoot it without you.
-I thought they could.
나도 그런 줄 알았는데
사실, 맥시는 식은 죽 먹기였어
The maxi-pads were a piece of cake.
Mini-pads should be that much easier.
미니가 장난이 아니라서 그렇지
- 발렌타인 데이야
- 알아, 일 때문이잖아
-It's Valentine's Day.
-I know, but it's my job.
일이 끝나는 대로
곧장 이리로 올게
I'll try to get back
as soon as I can.
미안해
그런데 요즘은 과학만
가르치고 있어요
I'm spending most of my time
teaching science...
웃기죠? 제 전공도
아니거든요
...which is funny because
that wasn't even my major.
정말 웃기네요
Now, that is funny!
저기요... 캐롤을 이리로
부르면 큰 실례가 될까요?
Do you think it would be too weird
if I invited Carol over to join us?
Because she's alone now.
And pregnant. And sad.
왜냐면... 지금 혼자고
임신중에다 우울해 보여서요
-I guess.
-Are you sure? Carol!
- 좋아요
- 정말이죠? 고마워요
캐롤!
이리 와서 같이 있자
-Wanna join us?
-No, I'm fine.
- 아냐, 괜찮아
- 아냐, 이리 와
Come on.
These people will scooch down.
사람들이 협조해줄 거야
어서 와
한 자리씩 옮길 수 있죠?
You guys will scooch, won't you?
Let's try scooching! Come on!
어서 합시다, 어서요
-Come on.
-Thank you.
고맙습니다
IKristen Riggs, this is Carol Willick.
Carol, Kristen.
크리스틴 릭스
이쪽은 캐롤 윌리
캐롤, 크리스틴이야
- 반가워요
- 저두요
-How do you do?
-Carol teaches sixth grade.
캐롤은 6학년 선생님이죠
그리고 크리스틴은...
And Kristen....
IKristen does something...
크리스틴은 뭔가를...
...that, funnily enough...
재밌게 한 대
...wasn't even her major!
전공도 아닌데 말야
-Thanks for coming over.
-Not at all. It's pretty much our job.
수고를 끼쳐 죄송해요
아뇨, 우리 직업이잖아요
That's why we get the cool hats.
그래서 방화복도 입었죠
-What do we got there?
-A piece of sik boxer shorts.
내용물이 뭐야?
비누 조각, 남자 팬티
축하 카드...
Some greeting cards.
반은 숯이 된 사진...
A half-charred picture of....
우리 대장보다 털이 많네
That guy's hairier than the chief!
어떻게 된 건지
말씀 드릴게요
It's a really funny story
how this happened.
I was taking out the trash,
and Phoebe was burning incense
쓰레기를 버리러 가는데
피비의 향이 타다 남아서...
됐습니다
설명하지 않아도 압니다
It's all right.
남자친구 물건들 화형식
하다가 화재도 종종 나죠
This isn't the first boyfriend bonfire
we've seen get out of control.
- 오늘만 벌써 세 건이에요
- 그래요?
-Third one tonight.
-Really?
발렌타인 데이가
가장 바쁜 날이에요
Valentine's is our
busiest night of the year.
앞으로, 물건 화형식을 할 땐...
Next time you're burning
your ex-boyfriend's stuff:
One, do it in a well-ventilated area.
제 1수칙, 야외에서 할 것
제 2수칙, 옷을 태울 시는
합성 섬유인지 확인할 것
Two, if you wanna burn his clothing,
stay away from synthetic fabrics.
Three, try to let go of the anger,
and learn to love yourself.
제 3수칙, 분노를 버리고
자신을 사랑할 것
선물 준비했어
-I brought you something.
-ls it loaded?
빵빵한 거야?
Oh, little candy hearts.
"Chan and Jan Forever."
사랑의 캔디!
'챈과 젠, 영원하라! '
I had them made special.
특별히 주문한 거야
Okay, Janice.
제니스
제니스...
Hey, Janice.
제니스?
어떻게 말해야할지 모르겠어
전에 해본 말인데도 모르겠어
There's no way to tell you this.
At least, there's no new way.
I just don't think things
are gonna work out.
우리가 잘 될지 모르겠어
That's fine.
괜찮아
It is?
그래?
이게 끝이 아니란 건 알거든
Because I know that this
isn't the end.
아냐, 이게 끝이야
You see, actually, it is.
끝이 아냐
No, because you won't let that happen.
너 때문에 끝날 수 없어
Don't you know it yet?
아직도 모르는 거야?
넌 날 사랑해, 챈들러 빙!
You love me, Chandler Bing!
Oh, no, I don't.
아니, 안 사랑해
Why do we keep ending up together?
New Year's, who invited who?
그럼 자신에게 물어봐
왜 우리가 자꾸 헤어지지?
신년 파티?
누가 누굴 초대했지?
-Valentine's, who asked who into bed?
-I did, but
발렌타인은?
누가 누구 침대로 초대했어?
- 내가 했지만...
- 넌 날 찾고 있어!
You seek me out!
네 영혼 깊은 곳에서
경적이 울려댄다구
Something deep in your soul
calls out to me like a foghorn!
제니스! 제니스!
Janice! Janice!
밀었다가도 다시 당긴다구
제니스!
You push me away,
you pull me back!
넌 날 원해!
날 필요로 한다구!
You want me. You need me.
넌 나 없이 못 살아!
You can't live without me.
And you know it.
그걸 알고 있지
You just don't know you know it.
너도 다 알면서, 모르는 거야
또 봐
See?
전화해!
Call me!
It's not true.
I never called your mother a wolverine.
너네 엄마를 애칭으로
부른 적 없어
그랬었어!
정말이야, 정말...
You did so, I swear to
화장실에 왜 이렇게
오래 있지?
How long has she been in the bathroom?
화장실 간 게 아냐
코트가 없잖아
She isn't in the bathroom.
Her coat's gone.
화장실이 춥나 보지
Well, maybe it's cold in there.
9년만에 본격적인
첫 데이트를 망치다니!
I screwed up my first date
in nine years.
- 그러게
- 세상에...
-That could be it.
-Oh, God.
여기 아직도 뜨겁다
You know, this is still pretty hot.
버섯 붙었어
Mushroom.
웃어
Smile.
언젠가 임자를 만날 거야
They won't all be like this.
Some might stay through dinner.
식사 마칠 때까지
있어줄 여자 말야
- 미안, 안 웃기지?
- 그게 아니라...
-I'm sorry. That's not funny.
-It's just....
인생을 열심히
살라는 말 알지?
You know the whole
"get on with your life" thing?
꼭 그래야 돼?
Well, do I have to?
예쁜 여자랑 함께 있었어
아주 좋은 여자야
I'm sitting here
with this cute woman...
...and she's perfectly nice, but that...
그런데... 여기에 없어
...that's it.
여기 앉아, 너와 대화를 하고
정말 즐거웠어...
Then I'm here talking to you,
and it's easy and it's fun.
내가 굳이 인연을...
And I don't have to....
- 알아
- 알아?
-I know.
-You know?
엉뚱한 생각이 났어
Here's a wacky thought.
우리 다시 잘해보자
Let's say you and I give it
another shot.
- 로스...
- 됐어, 무슨 말인지 알아
I know what you're gonna say.
You're a lesbian.
레즈비언!
이렇게 하자, 일단 그 말은
생각지 말자
But what do you say we just
put that aside for now.
여기 압정으로 박아 놔
Let's just stick a pin in it.
우리 서로 좋았잖아
그건 너도 인정하지?
Because we're great together.
You can't deny it.
너한테 딱 맞는 반지도 있고...
I've got a ring at home
that fits you.
사진도 많아
우리 둘이 함께 찍은 거
I've got lots of pictures
with both of us in them.
게다가 내 아이도 가졌어
And best of all,
you're carrying my baby.
- 완벽한 한 쌍이지
- 로스...
-I mean, how perfect is that?
-Ross
You keep saying that, but there's
something right here. I love you.
넌 자꾸 그 말만 하는데
내 말 좀 들어봐
사랑해
나도 사랑해
I love you too.
- 하지만...
- '하지만'은 빼 줘
-But
-No "but."
You know that thing we
put over here with the pin in it?
아까 저기 압정으로
박아 놓은 거...
이제 뺄 시간이야
It's time to take the pin out.
그래
좋은 짝을 만날 거야
인연이 어딘가에 있지
You'll find someone.
The right woman is waiting for you.
넌 짝을 찾았으니까
그렇게 말하겠지
It's easy for you to say.
You found one already.
남자를 좋아하는
여자만 만나면 다 돼
All you need is a woman who likes men,
and you'll be set.
저 여자 말고!
Not her.
정말 막대를 타고 내려오나요?
So, you guys really slide down a pole?
물론이죠
-Absolutely.
-That's so cool.
멋지네요
그럼 어떻게 올라가요?
How do you get back up?
불길이 치솟는 것보단
빨리 올라 가야죠
Well, we rarely have to return
from a fire as quickly.
저... 그러면... 언제 한번...
So, would you guys....
Would you like to, sometime, maybe....
술이나 한잔하죠
Go for a drink sometime?
네, 한잔 좋죠
Sure, sounds good.
거의 자정이 됐네요
그때 데리러 올게요
We get off at midnight.
We'll pick you up then.
- 좋아요...
- 좋아요
Okay. Great!
그럼...
소방차 타고 올 거죠?
So will you bring the truck?
I'll even let you ring the bell.
사이렌도 울리게 해줄게요
다음에 봐요
-We'll see you later.
-Bye! See you later!
잘 자요, 안녕
- 안녕히 가세요
- 네, 또 봐요
잘 가요
Oh, my God!
세상에!
정말 잘 됐어
See? There you go.
The cleansing worked.
- 의식이 효과가 있지?
- 맞아!
You're right. They're nice guys!
참 착해 보이지?
They're firemen guys!
소방관이잖아
- 기혼자라는 말했나?
- 아니
-Tell them you're married?
-No. My girlfriend doesn't even know.
우리 애인도 모르는데
그런 걸 왜 밝히겠어!